<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:02:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 001: Will I have a job five years from now?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-001-will-i-have-a-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-001-will-i-have-a-job/</guid>
      <description>Every translator today seems to be asking one question above all others. And the question is this&amp;ndash;will we continue to have jobs in the future? Or will machine translation, better translation software, more speech, voice and text translator apps—and who knows what else—eventually make our jobs obsolete? The answers may surprise you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 002: Why is Monterey called the language capital of the world?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-002-why-is-monterey-called-the-language-capital-of-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-002-why-is-monterey-called-the-language-capital-of-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Dino Pick, Chairman of Board of the Defense Language Institute, and Deputy City Manager of the City of Monterey, California, joins us to discuss why Monterey is known as the world’s language capital. And why a one-of-a-kind hub of linguistic talent is such a critical resource for national defense—and for global brand communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 004: Crowdsourcing - Convenience or Confusion?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-004-crowdsourcing-convenience-confusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:02:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-004-crowdsourcing-convenience-confusion/</guid>
      <description>Does crowdsourcing deliver on the promise of cost-saving convenience and quality assurance for localization managers? What happens when global brands rely on multiple translators with varied backgrounds? Does widespread collaboration actually help or hinder the workflow process—and the outcome? Renato and Michael discuss the pros and pitfalls of using crowdsourcing for translation and localization services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 005: How localization skyrockets growth</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-005-how-localization-skyrockets-growth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-005-how-localization-skyrockets-growth/</guid>
      <description>What happens when a young company uses localization as a primary growth strategy in its early expansion stages, instead of waiting until it builds greater brand recognition and a stronger global footprint? Georgia Vidler, localization manager for Canva, joins us to discuss how localization helped this Australian provider of online design tools gain 10 million users in a matter of months—and why localization continues to fuel skyrocketing growth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 006: Why is global branding so hard? And so worth it?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-006-global-branding-hard-worth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-006-global-branding-hard-worth/</guid>
      <description>Branding is one of the most common concepts in marketing, but it&amp;rsquo;s also one of the hardest to define. And when you consider branding from a global perspective, it&amp;rsquo;s even far more complex. In fact, there is no universal approach you can take to guarantee a successful global branding strategy. But the value and importance of a company&amp;rsquo;s brand reputation&amp;ndash;and its local voice, no matter where it&amp;rsquo;s heard&amp;ndash;are more than worth the effort involved in building a strong worldwide brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 007: An in-depth unconference report</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-007-in-depth-unconference-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-007-in-depth-unconference-report/</guid>
      <description>Show up. Participate. Be there. That’s all you need to do to make an unconference worth your time. But that doesn’t explain why unconferences are so popular in the language industry. Join Renato and Michael as they interview three industry pros who discuss how unconferences benefit LSPs. Learn how to make your own unconference successful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 008: Why don’t journalists use professional translators? A conversation with Lane Greene</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-008-why-dont-journalists-use-professional-translators-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-008-why-dont-journalists-use-professional-translators-conversation/</guid>
      <description>Lane Greene, the primary language reporter for The Economist and writer of the magazine&amp;rsquo;s Johnson language column, discusses translation from a journalism perspective. Why isn&amp;rsquo;t translation more frequently used to verify news sources, and what do journalists need from the language industry?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 009: When translation saves lives: The vision of Translators without Borders</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-009-translation-saves-lives-vision-translators-without-borders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-009-translation-saves-lives-vision-translators-without-borders/</guid>
      <description>The Ebola outbreak in Africa. The earthquake in Haiti. The countless children who die every day for lack of good nutrition. Join us as Lori Thicke tells the story of how she founded Translators without Borders. And how this amazing organization continues to educate, enrich and save lives. One language at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 010: What about sales?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-010-what-about-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-010-what-about-sales/</guid>
      <description>Join Renato and Michael as they discuss the ins and outs of selling in the LSP space. Key topics include price vs. cost, selling to novice vs. mature buyers, how sales have changed today and, most importantly, how to sell effectively at every stage of the buyer&amp;rsquo;s journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 011: What makes a world-class global marketing professional?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-011-makes-world-class-global-marketing-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-011-makes-world-class-global-marketing-professional/</guid>
      <description>What does it take to be a truly effective global marketer? Dr. Nitish Singh discusses the educational divide between digital marketing and localization&amp;ndash;and what LSPs can do to bridge the gap. Is certification the solution or is real-world experience enough? Join us as we take a closer look at this important issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 012: What does it mean to be truly global?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-012-mean-truly-global/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-012-mean-truly-global/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s the roadmap for elevating localization&amp;rsquo;s role in a global enterprise? In this episode we discuss best practices for success in international markets—and your career.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 013: Top localization dos and don&#39;ts</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-013-top-localization-dos-donts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-013-top-localization-dos-donts/</guid>
      <description>Renato and Michael share their opinions on the three top things localization professionals must and must not do to deliver optimum results. And value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 014: Localizing marketing content beyond borders</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-014-localizing-marketing-content-beyond-borders/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 21:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-014-localizing-marketing-content-beyond-borders/</guid>
      <description>Content may be king according to most B2B marketers today, but how do you keep the king from losing its power when multiple markets and dozens of different languages are involved? Excellence in localization and compelling content are the answers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 015: Unpacking localization strategies for a global hospitality brand</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-015-unpacking-localization-strategies-for-a-global-hospitality-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 22:02:43 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-015-unpacking-localization-strategies-for-a-global-hospitality-brand/</guid>
      <description>The 80&amp;frasl;20 rule. User-generated content. De-centralized translation management. Some of the strategies Marriott International uses to achieve its globalization goals are breaking new ground–not only for one of the world’s most respected brands, but also for the hospitality industry worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Podcast 003: How do top hospitality brands engage local travelers on a global scale?</title>
      <link>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-003-top-hospitality-brands-engage-local-travelers-global-scale/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 22:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://awesome-lumiere-1921ad.netlify.com/episodes/podcast-003-top-hospitality-brands-engage-local-travelers-global-scale/</guid>
      <description>Roughly 60% of international travelers now book their reservations online. Travelers who don&amp;rsquo;t find what they’re looking for right away are far more likely to become lost opportunities than confirmed reservations. Global travel brands aren’t the only ones feeling the pressure. So are LSPs who provide global travel companies with translations and destination-specific content under tighter and tighter deadlines. John Jimenez, Portfolio Director of e-Commerce at Interstate Hotels &amp;amp; Resorts, joins us to discuss how digital marketing has changed the travel industry’s marketing priorities—and what it means for LSPs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>